//stackoverflow Notes

super() calls the parent constructor with no arguments.
It can be used also with arguments. I.e. super(argument1) and it will call the constructor 
that accepts 1 parameter of the type of argument1 (if exists).
Also it can be used to call methods from the parent. I.e. super.aMethod()

The model is the central component of the pattern. 
It expresses the application's behavior in terms of the problem domain, independent of the user interface. 
It directly manages the data, logic and rules of the application.
A view can be any output representation of information, such as a chart or a diagram. 
Multiple views of the same information are possible, such as a bar chart for management and a tabular view for accountants.
The controller, accepts input and converts it to commands for the model or view.

"E" is for "effective." EJS is a simple templating language 
that lets you generate HTML markup with plain JavaScript. 

./ is the the folder that the working file is in:
So in /index.htm ./ is the root directory;
but in /css/style.css ./ is the css folder.

String is not a primitive array (so we can't use .length) 
and also not a Collection (so we cant use .size()) 
that's why we also need a different one which is 
length().

add() comes from Collection.
offer() comes from Queue.
For a capacity-constrained queue, the difference is that 
add() always returns true and throws an exception if it can't add the element, 
whereas offer() is allowed to return false if it can't add the element.

Map.Entry is a key and its value combined into one class. 
This allows you to iterate over Map.entrySet() 
instead of having to iterate over Map.keySet(), then getting the value for each key. 

自然排序（像int这种基本类型）因为有默认的Comparator存在，所以不需要加。
如果需要对自己定义的对象排序，那么我们就需要实现COmparator。
1）https://www.tutorialspoint.com/java/java_using_comparator.htm
这里有例子，且实现在类的里面，也相对容易一些，可以参考
2）Java自定义比较器
http://zhuhengwei.com/2016/02/27/Java自定义比较器实现中文排序/
这里也有例子，写的比较详细清楚，也可以参考

In Unix and related computers operating systems, 
a file descriptor (FD/fd) is an abstract indicator used to access a file 
or other input/output resource, such as a pipe or network connection. 
File descriptors are part of the POSIX application programming interface. 
A file descriptor is a non-negative integer, 
represented in C programming language as the type int.

makefile: On Windows with Notepad and the file extension, 
saved as type All types (".") from the drop down list and it got rid of the extension. 

If you want something simple that works but not elegant, you can use this code: 
int number = -782;
String numberAsString = "" + number;
When you concatenate a String and an integer, the result is a String. Internally, 
the code is inefficient because there're intermediate objects that are created behind the scene. 

如果我们要返回多个数据呢？
Class可以帮助我们解决这个问题，把多个数据封装起来.

Default constructor (默认构造函数)
1. 不带参数
2. 没有返回值（注：Java中，所有构造函数都没有返回值）
3. 如果没有函数体，写和不写是一 样的

Code that uses generics has many benefits over non-generic code: 
Stronger type checks at compile time. 
A Java compiler applies strong type checking to generic code and issues errors if the code violates type safety. 
Fixing compile-time errors is easier than fixing runtime errors, which can be difficult to find.

The anonymous class expression consists of the following:
		HelloWorld frenchGreeting = new HelloWorld() {...};
1. The new operator
2. The name of an interface to implement or a class to extend. In this example, the anonymous class is implementing the interface HelloWorld.
3. Parentheses that contain the arguments to a constructor, just like a normal class instance creation expression. 
   Note: When you implement an interface, there is no constructor, so you use an empty pair of parentheses, as in this example.
4. A body, which is a class declaration body. More specifically, in the body, method declarations are allowed but statements are not.

Besides operating on different stuff
(Collections.sort() operates on a List, and Arrays.sort() operates on an array), 
java.util.Collections.sort() simply calls java.util.Arrays.sort() to do the heavy lifting.
Also, for what it's worth, notice that Arrays.sort() runs a merge sort.

RSS (Rich Site Summary) is a format for delivering regularly changing web content. 
Many news-related sites, weblogs and other online publishers syndicate their content as an RSS Feed to whoever wants it.
